Pouya Mehrbabak

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran



pouya.mehrbabak@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/pouyamehrbabak

Summary

Currently, I testing Applications and doing manual QC and automated black-box UI testing using selenium.

Looking forward to getting more experience in QA and my goal is to set up a QA process and team to assure the quality of the product in each step of SDLC.

Graduate student of computer software engineering, Studying for a master's in computer science (soft computing and artificial intelligence). I Prefer Python for development and enjoy to work with Django.

Experience



Software Quality Assurance Specialist

ترىپ | Trip.ir

Sep 2022 - Present (4 months +)

- Communicate with teams to solve all related to the product
- Collaborate with Product and Design teams to make sure about specifications
- Collaborate with Backend and Frontend teams in code debugging
- Analyze the application to find performance issues and bugs
- Ideating to find efficient solutions for design and technical issues
- Writing Specifications and Acceptance Criteria and Reproduce Bug Steps

Junior Software QC Specialist

آوران پارسیانپیام | PAP Group Ltd

Jan 2022 - Sep 2022 (9 months)

- Did manual black box testing on products
- Created some automated scripts for projects with Selenium IDE
- Detected bugs, defects, and failures and did Bug tracking
- Did Quality Control of products

Web Development Intern

آوران پارسیانییام | PAP Group Ltd.

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022 (6 months)

- Modified FAQ contents and documents for customers and users
- Experienced deployment with NGinX and Django
- Designed Low Fidelity UX wireframes with Adobe XD and Figma
- Experienced SDLC in C# and ASP.Net and MVC architecture

Education



Islamic Azad University, Science And Research Branch

Master's degree of Computer science, Soft computing and artificial intelligence Oct 2021 - Present

Islamic Azad University Central Tehran Branch

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2015 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



Introduction to UX and UI - DUXLab

3188010727



Product Manager (PM) - Tose'e Higher Education Institute

14010616200



UX Design From Scratch - DUXLab

3188010820

Skills

Black Box Testing • Selenium • Problem Solving • Django • User Experience (UX) • Product Analysis